<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Fatuma Sharif</title><link>https://fatumasharif.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Fatuma Sharif</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:55:51 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fatumasharif.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Variables in Python</title><link>https://fatumasharif.github.io/posts/variables-in-python/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:55:51 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://fatumasharif.github.io/posts/variables-in-python/</guid><description>In programming, a variable is a storage location that is used to hold a value. This value can be a number, a string of text, or a complex data type such as a list or dictionary. Variables are useful because they allow us to store and manipulate data within our programs.
In Python, declaring a variable is as simple as assigning a value to it. For example:
`x = 5 message = &amp;#34;Hello World&amp;#34;` Here, we have created two variables: x and message.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with a Laravel Project</title><link>https://fatumasharif.github.io/posts/getting-started-with-laravel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:10:51 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://fatumasharif.github.io/posts/getting-started-with-laravel/</guid><description>Laravel is a powerful PHP framework that is designed to make it easy to build web applications. If you are new to Laravel and want to get started with your first project, here are the steps you need to follow:
Install PHP and Composer: Laravel is built with PHP, so the first thing you need to do is install PHP on your computer. You will also need to install Composer, which is a dependency manager for PHP.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://fatumasharif.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fatumasharif.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Projects Real Estate Website: Homely real estate website front-end design. view code
News App A simple news highlight application that pulls from news various sources such as BBC, CNN, Reddit, New York Magazine, and more. It is built on Flask framework View code
A School Website: Fictional Academy front-end design. view code
Blog: This blog
More to share soon&amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>